sun smarter life elite peso 10 this is
a participating whole life insurance
plan if the vul has an investment
feature its living benefit this is
the type of insurance plan that has a
savings feature its living
benefit what is the difference between investment
and savings investment is non
guaranteed fluctuating value
unsecured can make a profit can lose
savings guaranteed fixed the value is
fixed the income your only opponent here
is inflation since this is also
participating it can receive
dividends every year depending on the
income of the insurance company this
is a limited pay you only pay for 10 years
you are covered until age
100 you will still receive regular
cash payouts until age 100 these are the
details of the proposal the insured is
baby zero age the payor or the policy
owner or in this proposal the initial
owner is Mother age 40
non-smoker the premium is
100,100
this is the basis of the insurance and savings
feature of the plan there are two sides of
this product first the protection side
second the living benefit side or
the savings feature on the protection side
number one there is life insurance
covered there is baby the coverage PH
million next is Accidental Deb benefit
the coverage php500,000 covered is
baby number three total disability
benefit the purpose is to wave the
future premium the covered is baby when
disappointed
by terminal illness when baby has tanning
within 12 months number five
waver of premium upon debt or disability
of initial owner when
initial owner or parent has debt or disability
future premium
payments are now waved in living benefit number one
endowment cash payout this is 88% of the face
amount earlier which is is the
500,000 you will receive at the end of
the sixth policy year and every 2 years
until baby's age 100 88% of
php500,000 is
40,000 that will be 1.9 million this is
withdrawable once available you can also
just leave it in the account to earn that will be
192 per at age 100  baby's next
dividends this is an additional living
benefit but it is not guaranteed
It depends on the business
performance of the life insurance company
you can also withdraw it or use it
to pay future premiums or
buy additional Riders if
applicable or you can leave it in the
account to earn more interest
according to our friend at sunlife they
said the dividends were at 4.5% last year
in 202 3 next is the cash values ​​this is the
life blood of our policy this is the
total of our premiums but maturity
its value varies every year As
our policy lasts
it grows until it reaches
its highest value which is equal
to the value upon maturity in this case 1
million at baby's age 100 it is not
withdrawable But you can loan it
if you need to subject to the
interest rate and you have to pay
ways to get the cash values
number one insured must reach age 100
number two you loan the cash
values ​​or number three you terminate
the contract When it comes to the Return
of premium or the return of the  our
fallen it will take you 17 years
to return the total premium
based on the projection in the proposal
given to us provided number one
we do not take the cash payouts of the
endowment every 2 years
we only do rollover number two the dividend is 4.2%
and we do not take it
we just let it [ __ ]
every year number three there are no policy
loans the maximum potential living
benefit of this product is up
to
4,400 that's
44.3 million at age 100 provided number
one there are no withdrawals of the endowment cash
payouts it is only rollover number two there are
no withdrawals of the dividend
it is also only rollover number 3 At least
4.2% annual Dividend rates
consistently of the insurance company number
four there are no policy loans What are
its advantages on the protection side is
the waiver of premium for the parent in
case of death or disability during the
paying period within 10 years nothing to
understand at least in this policy
baby all the savings features
he will receive once available
Although When  It was not an
advantage to be
disappointed, the
financial benefits are guaranteed regardless of the
economic situations and we are sorry that
baby will receive the benefits no
matter what happened, just don't let
the insurance company close down. What are
the disadvantages of this on the
protection side? It is not strategic that the
insured is baby because
he is not the bread winner in case of a
debt from the parent or initial
owner. Baby will not receive immediate
financial assistance. That is the
crucial time because baby needs to be
promoted
to the savings feature side. Number one,
the return turn of premium is long, it will take up
to 17 years, provided there are no withdrawals of
endowment cash payouts, no withdrawals of
dividends.
Dividend rates are consistently 4.2%, no
policy loans. Number two, it is not that
competitive with other savings
or investments available in the market
today. Number three, the living benefits are locked and fixed
until baby's age 100. Do
you see yourself
reaching age 100 or baby reaching age
100? Number four, in case of
emergency, you cannot withdraw
the total in full.  Your premiums will be
contacted
[Music]
When it comes to the premium in this case
Php1,500 life insurance coverage for baby
that's 10% it's a bit expensive
mainly because it's a participating
whole life plan versus
our friend who we helped find
term life insurance whose
premium is only 0.42 of his life insurance out of his 1 million life
insurance
his premium is only 4,200 per year
of course it depends on age can
I recommend this important
question is it you sir ericel will you take
this product answer I don't
see myself taking this product
because number one
life insurance shouldn't be given to a minor because
he's not the bread winner of the family and
I'm not dependent on him number two
his premiums are too expensive for me it's not
worth it for my funds number three
I'm short on the living benefit or
its savings feature even though
it's guaranteed mainly because I
know that I have savings and investment
vehicles that give me a higher
return so with this product number four
The financial benefits and
baby's age 100 are locked opportunity wise I can't
immediately adjust if
there are good investment opportunities that come out
in the market overall it is not
strategic financially at least for me
To whom would you recommend this since
We have different principles and
beliefs when it comes to insurance especially
financial Capabilities I Believe
there are people who still like
this program especially if number
one it's okay SAO to give
your child life insurance number two
you have a budget and you can afford
his premiums number three you are satisfied
with the living benefit of the products number
four it's okay SAO that the
financial benefits are locked until baby's age 100
and you don't see a withdrawal
within 17 years things to consider
before buying this product number one
let's check the illustration
number six in the proposal This is what it
says This is a longterm insurance
product inflation over the years may
reduce the ability of the policy
coverage to offset a potential Loss in
the future number two since it's clear SAO
that this is a life insurance product do
you really need it  this is number
three what coverage and how much do
you need number four are you satisfied
with the benefits you saw number five can
your budget handle it if you see
this product for SAO message
our friend Rus frias of
sunlife Please check his FB profile in
the comment section below I hope
this product review was helpful to you for your
future decisions if you have questions
about your insurance policies or
are planning to get life insurance and
need advice just like us
on our Facebook account God bless
and hope to see you soon